I apologize for the inconvenience.
That's not a thank you.
Yay!
Today
I heard.
You two didn't go there the other day.
But I went to a restaurant called "KINOYA ISHINOMAKI SUISAN
I went with you.
I was thinking of going here for an interview.
Interview?
Niko-chu
Yes, sir.
There's a big traffic jam of blurbs.
Yes, well, let me get this straight.
It wasn't a blur.
LOL.
I'll make sure you two fill out your resumes.
Resume? I've never written one before.
You had an interview.
Wow, scary.
I see.
I'm sure you'll take it seriously.
Well, I'll write seriously now.
You're the most serious person I've ever met.
Yes, he's serious.
Yes, I'm serious.
By the way, have you ever written anything?
No, I haven't.
Have you?
Yes, I have.
Oh, I see.
Yes, you have.
Yes, I do.
I see.
Zunda.
Then, let's write a resume first.
Okay.
Let's take a look at the application outline.
What's this? I'm opening it for the first time, and I'm supposed to write all this?
You can write one. One.
This one?
Job Hunting Now.
That's great.
Hey!
Oh, wow.
That's great!
It's got all the great stuff written all over it.
No, no, no. Hey.
What's a resume?
Like the number of times you've been questioned.
That'll work.
Sakura-san took the common sense test the other day.
but...
But everyone was complaining about it.
What do you mean?
No, the person who should have taken it the hardest is missing.
What's the matter with you guys?
But I had a member do it for me this morning.
And I was able to do it.
That's right.
We all have common sense.
Understand?
Yes!
I was looking at the answer sheets.
I liked this one.
Sakura-san's "What do you think of purple?
When you say the word "purple", something comes up.
What is purple?
Only one of them said "to hold with the fingertips as if you have no body".
Really? How do you pull it together?
Who's that?
Who do you think?
Itchy.
Oh, ituya.
No, it's Ms. Mitsuki.
What? Oh, no.
That's funny.
It's funny, isn't it?
I'll start writing.
I'll write it down.
It's 2030, right?
Thirty years.
I wonder where we've been.
Indonesia.
What?
Twenty-one years.
Oh, okay.
[laughter at beginning]
Happy colorful muffins, Lucky Town, Yamagata Prefecture.
Theme of my life
Yamagata Prefecture
What time does elementary school start?
What time does it start?
From 8:15.
Around 9:00.
Mr. Fukushima, can you read aloud what you just wrote?Mr. Fukushima, may I ask you to read aloud what you just wrote?
Scheduled to enter the University of Tokyo in March 2023.
Please take a moment to look at the job application
Automotive installations
If you don't take a picture, you don't get in.
But it's not necessary at the time of application.
So you write that you'll take it eventually.
Reason for applying
Fuji
Favorite subject
Points that appeal to you
Cute
Cute.
How long is my commute?
But I can fly, so it's two minutes.
Why do you want to work here? I'm interested in fish.
You should join a fish research club.
A can of canned food has become the nation's confession.
I have the power to confess.
You know what I mean? Do you think I'm getting through to them?
I hope you get the message.
What's a spouse?
Ki no Ya... the bookstore.
Will they know?
Okay, it's done.
Yes! It's done.
Well, I'll take that with me, but since we're going to be here, I'll eat the canned food first.
That's right.
I've had it with a pile of whales since the time of your father and mother's ascension to the top of the industry.
Whale?
Whale.
Even whales.
It's a fun feeling.
Hey, whale!
Wow.
And they've been in business since 1957.
Two interviews?
You're going to do the same thing twice? Let's repeat that.
Bon appétit!
It's so good! Did you guys eat this?
Yes, I eat it with great relish!
And one more thing, Miyagi is all about the hut!
Hut is very fresh and very hard to find in the water!
That's right!
I heard this is a new product.
What? We're kids, is it okay?
It says "fresh adults.
Fresh adults?
Fresh adults? Which one is it?
Oh, my God, that smells good!
Oh, my God! Smells like seafood.
It's delicious! It's seafood.
Yeah! Yum! Yum!
Delicious!
I've written my resume, I've totally eaten already, and I've seen the job posting, so let's go get an interview!
Yes!
I have two interviews and aptitude test.
What's wrong with that? It's a common sense test. Can't you make it up?
Is that bad? It's a common sense test. Can't you make it up?
That's right.
If I give it to you, I'll fail.
Yo!
Let's go!
Yes, sir!
Come on! Yeah! Oh!
Are you nervous?
I'm nervous.
I don't know where I am.
I don't know my name.
Whoo!
You're not good!
Yes, sir!
Have a good day!
Excuse me!
Here you go.
Excuse me.
Yes, excuse me.
What is your name and school?
Yes, I go to Iwate City Municipal
I go to Inari High School in Iwate Prefecture.
Okay, I'll start the interview.
Yes, thank you very much.
First of all, you're interested in our company, right?
Why did you choose space?
My goal in life is to spread myself to the world.
I believe that the world is connected to the ocean.
Speaking of the sea, I think of fish, and speaking of fish, I think of canned food.
When I think of canned food, I think of our head office, and that's why I chose to work here.
Thank you very much.
Have you ever tried any of our products?
Yes, I have.
What did you buy?
Whale in Yamato and sea squirt.
How was it?
The seasoning was very good, just the way I like it.
Thank you very much.
What are you studying at school?
I study at school.
What do you study?What are you studying?
What do you study?
9 subjects
What is your favorite subject? Physical education.
Do you have good grades in PE? Yes, like a 5.
What do you mean by a 5? Sometimes 3.
You're a great student.
How did you get it?
I was born with the ability to make people smile.
You were born with it? Yes, that's right.
See, it made me smile. That's wonderful. Thank you.
It's nice. I hear it brightens up the office when Sakura-san joins us.
Yes, by all means.
I'm clearly curious about the last part. It says "University of Tokyo.
The University of Tokyo.
This is the year 2023, isn't it? I understand you're studying now.
Yes.
Is there a library in the school? You mean there is such a pavilion?
Yes, we do.
Yes, by all means!
What about this one?
Can I shake it?
What is it?
Especially since it's a song to cheer you all up.
Yes!
But I was wondering if I could just have a little bit here.
Is it possible to repeat it here?
Yes, I got it.
Fulop!
Goombale!
Gongombale, Gongombale! You can do it! You can do it!
Thank you very much.
Is it out?
It's a cry from the heart.
Thank you very much.
I look forward to working with you.
No problem.
Excuse me. Thank you very much.
Well, thank you again for meeting with us.
Thank you very much.
How's it going? To receive.
Well, he was very kind.
He didn't sing?
Did he ask you to sing?
I couldn't think of a melody right now.
But he was laughing a lot.
Well then, please wait in the waiting room for the announcement after we receive Mr. Fujitani, Mr. Gohey.
Yeah!
Yes! Excuse me. Please take care of them.
Thank you very much.
Okay, let's be natural for a minute.
Yes, sir.
While watching, right?
Yes.
Yes. I'm looking forward to it.
Then, please start with your name.
My name is Miyu Fujitani. I'm from Yamagata Prefecture.
I'm 16 years old and a sophomore in high school. I look forward to working with you.
Nice to meet you.
Are you from Yamamoto?
Yes, I am.
I'm sorry, I wasn't familiar with your address.
What is your self-address and what kind of place is it?
I'm in an idol group called Ikuta Geisha-san.
I'm a member of an idol group called Lucky Fujizany.
My life's theme is
Lucky Happy Colorful Smile.
I can't tell you my address on the air.
That's why I chose it.
I'm glad you said that.
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you very much.
First of all, where's your motivation?
I had a chance to try it before I came for the interview.
I had a taste of it before I came for the interview, and it really changed my image of canned food.
I wanted to be someone like that.
That's great. Thank you very much.
Do you know about my company?
Yes, I do.
What kind of company?
I took a look at your website.
I was struck by the variety of canned goods.
I was very impressed.
Which canned food did you like?
I really like the Yamatoni whale.
The sauce was so delicious.
I would like to take it home and eat it!
Thank you very much.
What subject are you good at in school?
I'm good at lunch.
Which part are you good at?
I'm good at serving.
What are your strengths and weaknesses?
My strength is that I really like to make people laugh.
My weakness is that I make people feel uncomfortable by being self-conscious.
I'm pretty genuine.
What is your specialty?Where are the Nagami specialties?
I sell a lot.
Do you have any questions?
Do you have any problems with KINOYA ISHINOMAKI FISHERY?
The problem is that our company has been dealing with whale for 64 years.
For everyone, it is difficult to taste the whale nowadays.
So how can we bring the taste and enjoyment of whale to your generation?
So, the problem is that I don't know how to convey the taste and enjoyment of whale to your generation.
I enjoyed whale so much, and the sauce was really delicious.
It changed my world.
It's really delicious, so let's do our best!
Can you tell me the most popular gag you've had recently?
I have a gag. Can I do it?
Yes, please.
I'd like to play an Indian ballerina.
Throw it away!
Yes, that's all.
Quick.
Speed is important.
Well, if there's nothing else, that's all.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
I understand.
Absolutely.
I don't know.
Let's just wait until the coffee is out.
It's like it's going to be announced just like that.
You know, like, "Poof!" with a cloth and you pass.
Or tererrere.
Yes, sir. Excuse me.
Excuse me.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
I got the impression that both of you are very friendly and fun people.
Yes, they are.
I think you have wonderful people who are very important to us.
Thank you very much.
It was a lot of fun. Today.
So, I would like to announce the results.
Yes.
I passed.
What?
Huh?
Both of you?
Yes.
What?
Let me tell you why.
It's the year 2023 in the history book, and you entered the University of Tokyo.
Four years of college.
Ah, yes.
We don't know what's going to happen in those four years, so I've talked with the president about taking it at this time.
I see. I understand.
As for Mr. Brittany, I really wanted to hire him, but after the interview, I looked at the history book again, and I found out that Mr. Brittany was going to be with us until the year 2060.
I looked at the history book again after the interview, and I found that he was supposed to stay at Sturgus until the year 2060.
No, I was very flexible.
What is your request?
Furokake.
Yes, sir.
I'm going back to the sea.
Excuse me.
Can I have it canned sometime?
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
I'll be back after I graduate from Tokyo University.
I'll be waiting for you.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
I'm the funny one.
I screwed up on my first message.
Let's try other companies.
Our challenge continues.
We'll start by writing a good history.
Failure is the basis of success.
Yes, failure is the source of success
Let's think positively.
Thank you very much.
That's all for now.
See you next week.
rock, paper, scissors!
Please subscribe to our channel.